

CONTACT

nagarajansvs@gmail.com

SKILLS

Html5 ------------Bootstrap5 -----**JavaScript** ------Jquery ---------------React JS -------**Typescript** *************** Sass & Tailwind *************** WordPress *************** PHP & Server ------Adobe Photoshop *************** Adobe Illustrator *************** Adobe XD & Figma *************

NAGARAJAN V

WEB DESIGNER

PROFILE

6+ years experienced Web Developer with proven success in building successful webpage & predictive models. To have a growth oriented and challenging career, where I can contribute my knowledge and skills to the organization and enhance my experience through continuous learning and teamwork.

EDUCATION

MCA, Thanjavur | AVVM Sri Pushpam College

Aug 2010 - Apr 2012

EXPERIENCE

Web Designer | Akk Line Media, Chennai

Aug 2023 - Present

- Closely worked with Business Analyst to understand the business requirements.
- Well versed in creating responsive web pages. PSD, Figma, Xd to HTML Conversion.
- · Created Marketing Related websites.
- · Created React js, Typescript Related websites.

Web Designer | Guardianlink (Appstar applications Pvt Ltd), Chennai Jun 2019 - Jul 2023

- Closely worked with Business Analyst to understand the business requirements.
- Created more than 100 Websites. Created Marketing Related websites.
 Created more than 50 Marketing Email templates.
- · Working on Crypto Development Websites.
- Working on Crypto Development User Panel & Admin Panel.
- Working on NFT Marketplace and Landing websites.
- · Working on Crypto Exchange websites.
- Well versed in creating responsive web pages. PSD Layout to HTML Conversion.

Web Designer | JustSee Info Service Pvt Ltd, Chennai

Jan 2017 - Jun 2019

- Closely worked with Business Analyst to understand the business requirements.
- Created more than 100 Websites.
- Created Marketing Related Websites.
- · Working on Content management System.
- Well Versed in Creating Responsive Web Pages.
- · PSD Layout to HTML Conversion. Design logos, brochures, banners, etc.

Web Designer | IndiaProperty Online Pvt Ltd, Chennai

Apr 2014 - Jun 2016

- Closely worked with Business Analyst to understand the business requirements.
- Created more than 50 Websites.
- Well Versed in Creating Responsive Web Pages.
- PSD Layout to HTML Conversion. Design logos, brochures, banners, etc.
- Created Mail Template and Signatures.

XML Operator | Amnet System Pvt Ltd, Chennai

Apr 2012 - May 2013

- Well Versed in Creating Responsive Web Pages.
- PSD Layout to HTML Conversion.
- Work alongside clients and help make their websites user-friendly and a great experience for their clients.

PORTFOLIO

https://worktual.co.uk

https://www.jump.trade

https://callit.jump.trade

https://pro.jump.trade

https://hurley.jump.trade

https://www.beyondlife.club

https://amitabh.beyondlife.club

https://www.fullyfaltoonft.com

https://pbm-coin.com

https://www.guardianlink.io

https://www.blockchainappfactory.com

https://www.cryptocurrencyexchangescript.com

https://www.eon8.com

https://www.appdupe.com

https://www.appstarsapplications.com

https://www.inoru.com

https://www.chaincella.com

https://www.infiniteblocktech.com

https://www.turnkeytown.com

https://www.polycruz.io

https://livenscience.com

http://www.ihafindia.org

https://ashvatthacapital.in

http://dynamicsolar.in

https://www.excelprodigy.com

https://mahalashmiwomenscollege.edu.in

https://botaliceblue.com

https://www.cityplots.io